Pamela Digby Churchill Hayward Harriman Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Part I: Personal and Family Papers, 1920-1997 (Box I:1-I:34)
  - Personal Papers, 1920-1997 (Box I:25-I:34)
    - Correspondence
      - Reagan, Ronald, 1993
      - Richards, Denis, 1973-1978
      - Roosevelt, Franklin D., 1942 [?]
      - Rothschild, Elie de, 1982
      - Shriver, Sargent and Eunice Kennedy, 1971-1978, 1991, undated
      - Sinatra, Frank, 1966-1974
      - Smith, Stephen E. and Jean Kennedy, 1963-1967, 1988-1990
      - Spiegel, Clara, 1975-1989
      - Staercke, André de, 1963-1965, 1976-1992, undated
      - Steinem, Gloria, 1977, undated
      - Stix, Hugh and Marguerite, 1972-1975, undated
      - Sulzberger, C. L., and family, 1965-1976, 1983-1991
      - Thatcher, Margaret, 1990-1993
      - Travell, Janet G., 1973-1980
      - Truman, Bess Wallace, 1971-1976, undated
      - Truman, Margaret, 1982-1983, 1992
      - Valéry, François, 1989-1992, undated
      - Vitalyevich, Dmitri, 1990-1997, undated, (6 folders)
      - Vreeland, Diana, 1964, 1971-1974, undated (Box I:33)
      - Walton, William ("Bill"), circa 1945, 1974-1992, undated
      - Windsor, Wallis Warfield, Duchess of, 1963-1965
    - Horoscope, 1955
    - Jansen Shop, New York, N.Y.
      - Address books, circa 1963-1967
      - Corporate records, 1963-1968, (2 folders)
      - Correspondence
        - Business, 1963-1968, undated
        - Personal, 1962-1967
      - Printed matter, 1963-1965
      - Receipts, 1961-1963, undated
    - Jewelry appraisal, 1982
    - Lists of family members, circa 1980s
    - Marriages
      - Churchill, 1939, 1946-1961
      - Harriman, 1971
        - Certificates and lists
        - Congratulatory letters, (5 folders) (Box I:34)
        - Note from W. Averell Harriman to Pamela Harriman
      - Hayward, 1960-1962
    - Miscellany, 1946-1947, 1958, undated
    - Passports and personal documents
      - Birth certificate, 1920, 1986
      - Driving documents, 1958, 1971-1974
      - Miscellaneous, 1971, 1990-1991
      - Naturalization, 1971-1972
      - Passports and visas, 1949-1993
    - Photographs
      - Churchill, Winston S. and Minnie d'Erlanger, 1964, 1971, 1983, undated
      - Harriman, Pamela
        - At Chequers, Buckinghamshire, England, 1943
        - Childhood, 1933, undated
        - President's birthday ball (photocopy), 1945
        - With
          - Harriman, W. Averell, 1971-1977, undated
          - Churchill, Winston S., 1942-1943, undated
      - Places, undated
      - Unidentified people, undated
    - Poem by Noel Coward, typescript, undated
- Part I: General Correspondence, 1951-1995 (Box I:35-I:180)
  - Alphabetical File, 1951-1995 (Box I:35-I:158)
    Correspondence and related material including agenda, minutes, reports, programs, speeches and writings by others, awards, photographs, and printed matter.
    Arranged alphabetically by name of person, organization, topic, or type of material.
    - "Aa-Ar" general, (7 folders) (Box I:35)
    - "As-Az" and "A" unidentified, (3 folders) (Box I:36)
    - Abell, Bess, 1983-1988, undated
    - Abramson, Rudy, 1982-1991
    - Abzug, Bella S., 1976-1991, (3 folders)
    - Ad Hoc Committee to Save the Sistine Ceiling, 1988
    - Adams, Brock, 1982-1991
    - Aga Khan, Sadruddin, 1986
    - Aggrey, O. Rudolph, 1978-1990
    - Alexander, Herbert E., 1980-1983
    - Alfred E. Smith Memorial Foundation dinner, New York, N.Y., 1984
    - Allbritton, Joseph L. and Barbara, 1977-1989
    - Alliance for Philanthropy, 1986
    - Allison, Graham T., 1982-1992, (2 folders) (Box I:37)
    - Alsop, Joseph and Susan Mary, 1972-1982, 1988, undated
    - Altmayer, Jay P. and Nan, 1981-1992
    - American Academy in Rome, 1992
    - American Air Museum in Britain, Duxford, England, 1992
    - American Cancer Society
      - Annual ball, Washington, D.C., 1985, (5 folders); (1 folder) (Box I:38)
      - General, 1976, 1983-1989
      - Humanitarian award, 1984
    - American Committee on U.S.-Soviet Relations, 1986-1988
    - American Foreign Service Association awards, 1983-1989, (6 folders)
    - American Foundation for AIDS Research, 1988
    - American Friends of English Heritage, 1988-1991
    - American Heritage Publishing Co., 1982-1983
    - American Horticultural Society, 1984-1992
    - American Intercultural Student Exchange, 1986, undated
    - American Political Foundation, 1979-1983, (2 folders) (Box I:39)
    - Andrus, Cecil D., 1976, 1986-1992
    - Angolite and Wilbert Rideau, 1976-1985, (2 folders)
    - Annenberg, Lee and Walter, 1967, 1974-1980, 1989-1990, undated
    - Architectural Digest, 1983-1984
    - Arms Control Association, 1982-1988, (2 folders)
    - Art Against AIDS, 1987-1990
    - Aspin, Les, 1973-1993, (4 folders) (Box I:40)
    - Association of American Foreign Service Women, 1985
    - Atlantic Council of the United States
      - 1985-1987, (7 folders)
      - 1988-1989, (12 folders) (Box I:41)
      - 1990, (8 folders) (Box I:42)
      - 1991, (3 folders); (5 folders) (Box I:43)
      - 1992, (6 folders); (2 folders) (Box I:44)
      - 1993-1995, (2 folders)
    - Auburn Mills shopping mall project, Auburn Hills, Mich., 1990-1992, (2 folders)
    - Avis Bohlen Award, 1981-1989
    - "Ba" general, (4 folders)
    - "Be-Bi" general, (7 folders) (Box I:45)
    - "Bl-Br" general, (10 folders) (Box I:46)
    - "Bu-By" general, (3 folders) (Box I:47)
    - Bagley, Smith and Elizabeth, 1976-1990
    - Baird, Barbara, 1986-1992, undated
    - Baliles, Gerald L., 1985-1992, undated, (6 folders)
    - Ball, Robert M., 1985
    - Barbados, 1983-1993 (Box I:48)
    - Barford, Margaret, 1982-1985
    - Barone, Joan Shorenstein, 1981-1984
    - Barry, Marion, 1981-1989, (2 folders)
    - Bates, Jim, 1987
    - Batten, William M., 1981-1987
    - Baucus, Max, 1979-1992
    - Bauer, Robert F., 1985-1988, undated
    - Bayh, Birch, 1971-1988, undated
    - Bayh, Evan, 1985-1992
    - Benton, Charles and Marjorie, 1981-1992
    - Bentsen, Lloyd, 1980-1992
    - Berger, Samuel R., 1980-1992, undated, (2 folders)
    - Bergreen, Bernard D., 1988-1989
    - Bernhard, Berl, 1980-1989
    - Better World Society, 1985-1986, undated
    - Bialer, Seweryn, 1983-1986
    - Biden, Joseph R., 1977-1990, undated
    - Billings, Leon G., 1978-1989, undated, (3 folders) (Box I:49)
    - Billington, James H., 1981-1992, undated
    - Billington, Joy, 1976-1992, undated
    - Bingham, Jonathan B., 1971-1986, undated
    - Bipartisan Committee to Study Methods of Financing National Nominating Conventions, 1973-1974
    - Birchgrove ("Haywire House"), Yorktown Heights, N.Y., circa 1971, 1982, 1989, undated
    - Blanchard, James J., 1986-1993
    - Block, Herbert, 1984-1987
    - Boggs, Lindy, 1981-1990
    - Bohlen, Avis, 1971-1980, 1992, undated
    - Book requests, 1988
    - Books Across the Sea, 1989
    - Bowles, John, IV, 1979-1992, undated, (3 folders)
    - Bradlee, Benjamin C., 1977-1978, 1988-1990 (Box I:50)
    - Bradley, Bill, 1982-1992
    - Bradley, Tom, 1983-1986, undated
    - Brandon, Henry and Muffie, 1973-1992, undated, (2 folders)
    - Breaux, John, 1983-1992, undated
    - Breaux, Lynn, 1992-1993
    - Brinkley, David and Susan, 1972-1982
    - British election, 1983
    - Bronfman, Edgar M. and Sherry, 1975-1992, undated, (2 folders)
    - Brookings Institution
      - Binders
        - 1987-1989, (4 folders)
        - 1991-1993 (Box I:51)
      - General
        - 1986-1989, (10 folders)
        - 1990-1993, (7 folders) (Box I:52)
      - Japan-U.S. Partnership Forum, 1988-1990, (3 folders)
      - Printed matter, 1984-1988 (Box I:53)
      - Seventy-fifth anniversary, 1990-1991, (5 folders)
      - W. Averell Harriman Chair, 1991-1993
    - Brown Brothers, Harriman & Co., circa 1985, undated
    - Brown, J. Mayo, regarding Middleburg, Va. property, 1986-1993
    - Brown, Jean, 1991-1993
    - Brown, Jerry, 1982-1983
    - Brown, John Y., and Phyllis George, 1981-1985, undated
    - Brown, Ronald Harmon, 1989-1993 See also Part I: Oversize
    - Brown University, Providence, R.I., John Carter Brown Library, 1987-1992, (2 folders)
    - Bruce, Evangeline and David, 1973-1992, undated (Box I:54)
    - Brzezinski, Zbigniew, 1976-1981, undated
    - Buchwald, Art and Ann, 1971-1988
    - Bumpers, Dale, 1981-1991
    - Bundy, McGeorge and Mary L., 1975-1991
    - Burbulis, Gennady, 1993
    - Burdick, Quentin N. and Jocelyn Birch, 1982-1992
    - Bush family, 1976-1977, 1989, undated
    - Byrd, Robert C., 1981-1992, undated
    - "Cab-Cam" general, (4 folders)
    - "Can-Che" general, (13 folders) (Box I:55)
    - "Chi-Co" general, (17 folders) (Box I:56)
    - "Cr-Cy" general and "C" unidentified, (7 folders) (Box I:57)
    - Cahan, Grace and William G., 1972-1992, undated
    - Cahen, Alfred J. and Nicole, 1979-1984, 1990
    - Calhoon, Jesse M. and Jean, 1980-1985
    - Californians Against Street Crime, 1982
    - Candidate thank-you letters, 1983-1988, (4 folders)
    - Candon, Mary Eva, 1982-1990
    - Capital Children's Museum, Washington, D.C., 1980-1985
    - Carlough, Edward J., 1984-1992 (Box I:58)
    - Carnegie Corp. of New York, 1984-1988, (2 folders)
    - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, 1988-1990, (3 folders)
    - Carter, Jimmy and Rosalynn
      - Correspondence See Container I:26, Carter, Jimmy and Rosalynn
      - Inauguration, 1976-1977
      - Presidential campaigns, 1976-1980, (3 folders)
      - Presidential library and center, Atlanta, Ga.
        - 1983, (3 folders)
        - 1985-1991, (2 folders) (Box I:59)
      - Speeches, 1980
    - Castro, Bette and Nash, 1973-1992, (2 folders)
    - Caulkins, Dan Platt, 1976-1985
    - Center for National Policy, 1982-1989, (3 folders)
    - Center for Strategic and International Studies, 1987-1988, (5 folders)
    - I:2Center for the Study of the Presidency, 1988
    - Century Association, 1988-1992 (Box I:60)
    - Chaffee, Kevin, Washington, D.C., map book, contribution by Pamela Harriman, 1991
    - Challinor, Joan Ridder, 1981-1992
    - Chancellor, John and Barbara, 1976-1989
    - Charles A. Lindbergh Fund, 1984-1987
    - Chatham House, Royal Institute of International Affairs, 1988-1990
    - Chayes, Antonia Handler, 1977-1992
    - Chiang Kai-Shek, Madame, 1982, 1989
    - Children's Defense Fund, 1986-1989
    - Children's Health Fund, 1989
    - China, 1973-1988, undated
    - Christmas
      - Incoming letters, 1986-1987
      - Special notes, 1986-1987
    - Church, Frank and Bethine, 1972-1992, (2 folders); (4 folders) (Box I:61)
    - Churchill College, Cambridge, England, 1971-1975, 1985-1988
    - Churchill, Winston
      - "The Dream," typescript and published edition, undated
      - General, 1983-1995, undated, (2 folders)
      - International Churchill Society
        - 1985-1990, (2 folders)
        - I:31991-1993
      - Winston Churchill Foundation of the United States, 1987-1993 (Box I:62)
      - Winston Churchill Memorial and Library, Westminster College, Fulton, Mo., 1972, 1982-1992
      - Winston Churchill Travelling Fellowships Foundation, 1988-1992, (3 folders)
    - Cisneros, Henry G., 1983-1984
    - Citizens' Committee for Immigration Reform
      - 1981, (2 folders)
      - 1982, (2 folders) (Box I:63)
    - Citizens' Research Foundation, 1983-1990, (10 folders)
    - Clarke, Gerald, 1977-1987
    - Clifford, Clark M. and Marny
      - 1972-1983
      - 1984-1993, undated, (2 folders) (Box I:64)
    - Coelho, Tony, 1980-1991, undated See also Part I: Oversize, (2 folders)
    - College of William and Mary, Williamsburg, Va.
      - 1985, (3 folders)
      - 1986, (5 folders); (10 folders) (Box I:65)
      - 1987, (12 folders); (3 folders) (Box I:66, Box I:67)
      - 1988, (8 folders); (5 folders) (Box I:68)
      - 1989, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box I:69)
      - 1990-1993, undated, (5 folders)
    - Columbia College, Chicago, Ill., honorary degree, 1984 (Box I:70)
    - Columbia University, New York, N.Y.
      - General, 1982-1990, (7 folders)
      - Harriman Institute
        - 1981-1987, (6 folders)
        - 1988-1993, undated, (9 folders) (Box I:71)
      - Honorary degree, 1986-1987 (Box I:72)
    - Commission on Peace, 1985
    - Committee for National Security, 1983-1989, (2 folders)
    - Committees, miscellaneous, 1974-1989
    - Condolences sent, 1990, undated
    - Congratulatory letters on the 1992 election, 1992
    - Congressional Award Program, 1979-1985, (4 folders)
    - Congressional Wives Club, 1983-1984
    - Contributions
      - Given
        - 1989
        - 1990-1991, (4 folders) (Box I:73)
      - Regretted, 1972-1980, 1990-1991, (4 folders)
    - Cookbook project, 1984
    - Cooper, Chester L., 1976-1989 (Box I:74)
    - Cooper, John Sherman and Lorraine, 1972-1991, undated
    - Council on Competitiveness, 1988
    - Council on Foreign Relations
      - 1985-1988, (10 folders)
      - 1989-1993, undated, (5 folders) (Box I:75)
    - Cowles, Gardner and Jan, 1971-1977, 1985-1990
    - Cranston, Alan, 1979-1992, undated
    - Crawley, Harriet, 1978-1988, undated
    - Cronkite, Walter, 1981-1983, 1990-1992
    - Cuomo, Mario M., 1980-1991, undated, (4 folders) (Box I:76)
    - "Da-De" general, (13 folders)
    - "Di-Dz" general, (19 folders) (Box I:77)
    - I:4Daschle, Thomas and Linda Hall, 1982-1992
    - Dayton, Mark B., 1981-1991 (Box I:78)
    - Deafness Research Foundation, 1983
    - Denmark, 1985-1987
    - Dickerson, Nancy, and John Whitehead, 1972, 1982-1992, undated
    - District of Columbia
      - Abused women, 1977
      - Democratic State Committee, 1982-1985, 1993, undated See also Part II: Oversize
      - Municipal government, 1982
      - Presidential inauguration "no parking" signs See Part I: Oversize
    - Dixon, Alan J., 1981-1990
    - Dodd, Christopher J., 1981-1992
    - Donation requests, 1987, (3 folders)
    - Douglas, William, 1987
    - Dukakis, Michael S., 1982-1989, (2 folders)
    - Duke, Angier Biddle and Robin, 1974-1992
    - Dwight David Eisenhower Centennial Commission, 1990-1993 (Box I:79)
    - Dyhrenfurth, Norman Gunter, 1963-1964, 1974-1988
    - Dyson, Charles H., and family, 1984-1992
    - "E" general, (11 folders)
    - E. H. Harriman Memorial Awards Institute, 1984-1991
    - Eisenhower World Affairs Institute, 1988-1989
    - Eizenstat, Stuart, 1977-1991, undated, (3 folders) (Box I:80)
    - Eleanor Roosevelt Centennial Celebration, 1982-1984
    - Engelhard, Jane, 1973-1991
    - English Speaking Union, 1988-1993, (8 folders)
    - Enterprise Foundation, 1984-1992, (2 folders) (Box I:81)
    - Erburu, Robert F., Times Mirror Co., 1988-1993, (3 folders)
    - Eskind, Jane, 1982-1989
    - Europe '92, 1989
    - Evans, James H. and Rosemary, 1977-1991
    - Evans, John V., 1982-1986
    - Executive Mansion Preservation Society, 1984-1989
    - Exon, J. James, 1982-1990 (Box I:82)
    - "Fa-Fore" general, (18 folders)
    - "Forg-Fut" general, (15 folders) (Box I:83)
    - Family Center, Washington, D.C., 1974-1975, undated, (3 folders)
    - Feinberg, Abraham
      - 1981-1991, (2 folders)
      - 1992, (2 folders) (Box I:84)
    - Feldman, Trude B., 1973-1984
    - Feller, Gordon, 1982-1987
    - Fenn, Peter, 1982-1990
    - Ferraro, Geraldine, 1982-1992, (2 folders)
    - Ferry Farm, Stafford County, Va., 1990
    - Foley, Thomas S. and Heather, 1981-1992
    - Foreign Press Association, 1983-1993
    - Foundation requests, 1981
    - Foxcroft School, Middleburg, Va., 1982-1983, 1991
    - Francis, Richard, 1985
    - Franklin and Eleanor Roosevelt Institute
      - 1987-1988, (2 folders)
      - 1989-1993 (Box I:85)
    - Franklin D. Roosevelt Four Freedoms Foundation, 1983-1991
    - Franklin D. Roosevelt Library, Hyde Park, N.Y., 1991-1992, undated
    - Franklin Delano Roosevelt Memorial Commission, 1991-1993
    - Freeman, Orville L. and Jane, 1974-1991
    - French Fashion Academy, New York, N.Y., 1985-1992
    - Friedman, Philip J., 1982-1988
    - Friendly, Alfred and Jean, 1971-1988
    - Friendly, Alfred, Jr., and Pie, 1981-1991, undated
    - Fritchey, Clayton and Polly, 1975-1990
    - Fulbright, J. William, 1974-1992
    - Funding the Prevention of Nuclear War, 1982
    - "Ga-Gon" general, (20 folders) (Box I:86)
    - "Good-Gwe" general, (17 folders) (Box I:87)
    - G. Heywood Hill book dealers, 1984
    - Galbraith, John Kenneth
      - 1973-1984
      - 1985-1992 (Box I:88)
    - Gamage, Stewart, 1986-1991
    - Garden Club of America, 1984-1987
    - Garden tours, 1984-1988
    - Gardener magazine, 1984
    - Gardner, Richard N., 1984-1992
    - Gates, Jeffrey R., 1983-1989
    - George C. Marshall Foundation and related material, 1972-1976, 1985-1993, (4 folders)
    - George Washington University Medical Center, Washington, D.C., 1989-1992 (Box I:89)
    - Georgetown garden tours, 1985-1987, undated
    - Georgetown residence, 3038 "N" Street, N.W., Washington, D.C.
      - Energy efficiency, 1977
      - Miscellany, 1983-1990
      - Sketch of house, 1990-1992
    - Georgetown University, Washington, D.C., 1981-1990
    - Georgetown Waterfront Arts Commission, 1986-1988
    - Gephardt, Richard A., 1981-1993, (2 folders)
    - Germany, 1989-1990
    - Glenn, John, 1979-1991, undated, (2 folders)
    - Glover, Katherine D. W., 1982-1986
    - Goldman, Guido, 1975-1992
    - Goodman, Edmund N. and Marian, 1972-1991
    - Goodman, Zmira, 1982-1985
    - Gore, Al, 1981-1993, undated, (3 folders) (Box I:90)
    - Graham, Bob, 1985-1993
    - Grants, thank-you letters, 1983
    - Gray, William H., III, 1985-1989
    - Green Door
      - 1976-1980, (7 folders)
      - 1981-1992, undated, (10 folders) (Box I:91)
    - Grenada, 1986 (Box I:92)
    - Gridiron Club, Washington, D.C., dinner, 1987
    - Groome Center, Washington, D.C., 1977
    - Groton School, Groton, Mass., 1988-1990
    - Growe, Joan Anderson, 1984-1985
    - "H-Harr" general, (11 folders)
    - "Hart-Holt" general, (19 folders) (Box I:93)
    - "Hom-Hy" general and "H" unidentified, (12 folders) (Box I:94)
    - Hammer, Armand and Frances, 1977-1990
    - Harding, Harry, 1987-1988
    - Harkin, Tom, 1981-1991
    - Harriman Cup polo match, 1987-1989
    - Harriman family foundations
      - Mary W. Harriman Foundation, 1987-1993
      - W. Averell and Pamela Harriman Foundation, 1982-1991
    - Harriman Society, Westchester Co., N.Y., 1986-1991 (Box I:95)
    - Harriman State Park, Ashton, Idaho, 1983-1989
    - Harriman Trail, Idaho, 1991-1993
    - Harriman, W. Averell
      - Awards, 1983-1985
      - Centennial celebration, 1991
        - Film
        - General planning, (3 folders)
        - Library of Congress symposium (Box I:96)
          - Dinner, (2 folders)
          - Symposium, (2 folders)
        - Replies, (3 folders)
        - Woman's National Democratic Club, Washington, D.C., luncheon, (2 folders) (Box I:97)
      - Documentary, 1988-1989
    - Harris, Lou, 1983
    - Harry Hopkins Public Service Institute, 1986-1992
    - Harry S. Truman Library, Independence, Mo., 1985-1987
    - Hart, Gary, 1977-1988, undated, (2 folders)
    - Hart, Peter D., 1981-1991
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass., 1983-1992, (2 folders)
    - Hay, Jess, 1982-1989 (Box I:98)
    - Hayden, Tom, and Jane Fonda, 1983-1985, undated
    - Heinz, Henry John, II, and Drue, 1971-1989
    - Helms, Richard and Cynthia, 1977-1992
    - Holbrooke, Richard C., 1975-1992
    - Hollings, Ernest F. ("Fritz") and Peatsy, 1977-1989
    - Holtzman, Elizabeth, 1974-1982
    - Hopkins, Harry, 1989-1991
    - Hopkins, Sean, 1986
    - Horticultural Society of New York
      - 1972-1979, (6 folders)
      - 1980-1985, (13 folders) (Box I:99)
      - 1986-1991, (3 folders) (Box I:100)
    - Hospice Care of the District of Columbia, 1985-1991
    - Howard, Anne L., 1981-1989
    - Hughes, G. Philip, undated
    - Humphrey, Hubert H. (1911-1978), 1976-1985
    - Humphrey, Hubert H. (1942- ) ("Skip"), 1982-1988
    - Hunt, Jim, 1981-1992
    - "I" general, (3 folders)
    - Idaho Foundation for Parks and Lands, 1990
    - Initiative for Conflict Management in Russia, 1990-1992, undated
    - Institute for East-West Security Studies, 1987-1989
    - Institutional Development Corp., 1977-1978 (Box I:101)
    - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1987-1988
    - International Castles Institute, 1989
    - International Human Rights Law Group, 1984-1988
    - International Institute for Women's Political Leadership, 1988-1989
    - International Women's Year, 1975-1977
    - Invitations to swearing-in and inaugural events, 1986-1987, (2 folders)
    - "Jac-Jon" general, (11 folders)
    - "Jor-Jun" general, (2 folders) (Box I:102)
    - Jackson, Jesse, 1987-1988
    - Jacobs, Harry A., Jr., 1982-1992, (2 folders)
    - James Smithson Society, 1977-1980, (2 folders)
    - Japan
      - General, 1987-1993
      - Letters to Bill Clinton and Al Gore, 1992
    - Joan Shorenstein Barone Center, Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass.
      - 1985-1988, (2 folders)
      - 1989, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box I:103)
      - 1990-1992, (2 folders)
    - Joan Shorenstein Barone Memorial Fund, 1983-1985
    - Joint Center for Political Studies, 1984-1989, (2 folders)
    - Jonas, Jeanne E., 1971-1992
    - Jordan, Hamilton, 1985-1986, undated
    - Junior League
      - Christmas shop, 1983
      - Community Advisory Committee, 1974-1980, 1989, (3 folders)
    - "Ka-Kl" general, (15 folders) (Box I:104)
    - "Kn-Ky" general, (7 folders) (Box I:105)
    - Kalb, Marvin, 1985-1992
    - Kennan, George F., 1951, 1983-1992
    - Kennan Institute
      - 1983-1985, (2 folders)
      - 1986
        - Jan.-Oct., (2 folders)
        - Nov.-Dec. (Box I:106)
      - 1987-1993, (7 folders)
    - Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts, 1976-1992
    - Kentucky Derby, 1982
    - Kerry, John, 1984-1991
    - Keyserling, Leon H. and Mary Dublin, 1984-1989
    - Kipper, Judith, 1988-1992 See also Classified
    - Kirk, Paul G., 1983-1992, undated, (3 folders) (Box I:107)
    - Kirschenbaum, Bruce, 1987-1992
    - "La-Ler" general, (13 folders)
    - "Les-Lyn" general, (12 folders) (Box I:108)
    - Laka, Eugene J., 1986
    - LaRouche, Lyndon H., 1982-1991, undated
    - Lautenberg, Frank R., 1982-1992
    - Lawyers Alliance for World Security, 1991-1992
    - Leahy, Patrick J., 1982-1992
    - Lewis, Flora, 1984-1987
    - Liang Yuhua, 1986-1993
    - Liberty Medal, 1986 (Box I:109)
    - Library of Congress, 1976-1993
    - Long, Carolyn and Russell B., 1980-1989
    - Loudoun County Democratic Committee, 1983-1992, (3 folders)
    - Lyndon Baines Johnson Library, Austin, Tex., 1982-1988
    - "Mab-Mars" general, (7 folders)
    - "Mart-McM" general, (14 folders) (Box I:110)
    - "McN-Moy" general, (13 folders) (Box I:111)
    - "Mr-My" miscellaneous (Box I:112)
    - Manatt, Charles T., 1981-1990, undated
    - Manchester, William, 1961, 1982-1991
    - Mandela, Nelson, 1990-1993
    - Marshall Plan, fortieth anniversary, 1987-1988
    - Mason, Christopher, song dedicated to Harriman, 1988
    - Mathias, Charles McC., 1971-1991
    - Maxwell, David O., 1988-1992
    - McCurdy, Dave, 1987-1993
    - McKenzie, Ruth Bates, "Welcome to Welfare" musical, 1989
    - McPherson, Harry, 1981-1986
    - Menninger Foundation
      - 1980-1982, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box I:113)
      - 1983-1984, (8 folders)
      - 1985-1988, (9 folders) (Box I:114)
      - 1989, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box I:115)
      - 1990-1992, (4 folders)
    - Middleburg Hunt, 1987-1993
    - Middleburg, Va.
      - General, 1983-1993
      - Willow Oaks estate, 1986-1991, undated
    - Mikulski, Barbara A., 1984-1992
    - Miller, Herbert S. and Patrice, 1988-1990
    - Mirabella, Grace, 1990-1992
    - Mirsky, Georgiy I., 1990-1992
    - Mitchell, George J., 1982-1990 (Box I:116)
    - Mondale, Walter F., 1976-1990